# Nick Yang (Li-Cheng Yang, 楊立誠)

nick10811@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick10811/ | https://nick10811.github.io

#### Profile

I am a software engineer. Although I like to develop iOS Apps [1], I am involved in backend and frontend developments as well. Those experiences helped me have a comprehensive insight into product development. As a team player, I am familiar to observe the circumstances of the team and propose my solution to improve teamwork. It is my pleasure if I can make team better.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Trend Micro Inc.

Taipei, Taiwan

Senior Engineer

Jun 2022 - present

- Build the system architecture of the job queue on MGCP in 2 weeks.
- Build microservices using gRPC, AWS Kafka.
- Lead a new project in the blockchain team and plan the product's future.
- Study the source code of open-source tools, Mythril, Slither, and integrate them into our product.
- Make a training workshop for juniors.

#### Shoalter Technology Ltd.

Taipei, Taiwan

Oct 2021 - Apr 2022

- Senior Programmer
  - Technical instruction on the iOS team. [1]
    Make development & code review guidelines for engineers to follow.
  - Lead code refactoring on existing projects in the 5 members team.
  - Lead the team to migrate to Swift to reach 86% coverage.
  - Improve enterprise release processing time by 90%.
  - Discuss requirements & features among cross-department.
  - Lead a study club of SwiftUI in the company.

Lubn Inc.

Tainan, Taiwan

Senior Software Engineer

Jul 2018 - Sep 2021

- Independent develop 2nd version iOS App and design MVVM, MVVMC architecture. [1]
- Add unit test & API test to existing projects.
- Reduce more than 1 hour deployment time through implementation of CI/CD with Jenkins, Docker, and Fastlane.
- Discuss API design with the backend team to fit requirements.
- Build PWA using ReactJS and Redux. [3]

### AsianArk Technology Inc.

Taipei, Taiwan

iOS Developer

Sep 2017 – Mar 2018

- Maintain and improve features on existing gambling App. [2]
- Design code architecture of the new App & develop fantastic UI in 1 month. [2]
- Make coding conventions on the iOS team.
- Develop chatroom & immediate update odds using WebSocket.
- Display the live view using embedded WebView.

# Changing Information Technology Inc.

Hsinchu, Taiwan

Oct 2014 - Aug 2017

Software Engineer

- Develop Universal App, watchOS App, and static library. [1]
- Add storyboard & AutoLayout to existing iOS project.
- Develop Bluetooth unlock the iOS App feature.
- Develop RESTful API using Jersey.
- Design event-based (iNotify) & polling algorithm to implement cloud-sync.

#### **EDUCATION**

# National Chung Hsing University

Taichung, Taiwan

MS in Department of Management Information Systems. (CS)

2014

The member of Network Security Laboratory. [4]

# Providence University

Taichung, Taiwan

BS in Department of Computer Science and Information Management.

2012

# SKILLS

# References

- [1] Latest App (https://nick10811.github.io/latest\_app/)
- [2] Unpublished App (https://www.beckydesign.com.tw/d9/index.html)
- [3] Lubn Dashboard (https://lubn.app)
- [4] Publications (https://nick10811.github.io/publication/)